Commencement Programs UP037
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Combined Commencement programs, 1857 -- 2021; UP037.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 148 Digital Object(s); 0.98 Gigabytes
  - 165th Commencement, 2021 May 23; UP037.000107 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 164th Commencement Ceremony, 2022 May 27; UP037.000109; 0.1 Linear Feet 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 22)
    This program was created for the 164th Commencement Ceremony, which was held on May 27, 2022 due to the Covid-19 pandemic.
  - 166th Commencement, 2022 May 22; UP037.000110; 0.1 Linear Feet 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Doctoral Hooding Ceremony, 2002 -- 2006; UP037.002; 0.25 Linear Feet
  The Doctoral Hooding ceremony was initiated in 1998 in order to celebrate the accomplishments of students in Arts and Sciences who are receiving their doctorates. In 2006 candidates for the Occupational Therapy Doctorate graduated for the first time. Also in 2006 the name of the ceremony was changed from Ph.D. Hooding to Doctoral Hooding.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Programs from the Doctoral Hooding Ceremony, 2002 -- 2006; UP037.002.001 (Box 1)
    Missing program for 2004.
- Graduate School Commencement programs, 1970 -- 2008; UP037.003; 1.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains commencement programs of individual graduate schools associated with Tufts University.
  - Commencement Programs, 1970; UP037.003.003.00001 (Box 3)
    Missing: School of Dental Medicine
  - Commencement Programs, 1972; UP037.003.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1974; UP037.003.003.00003 (Box 3)
    Missing: Fletcher School
  - Commencement Programs, 1975; UP037.003.003.00004 (Box 3)
    Missing: School of Medicine
  - Commencement Programs, 1976; UP037.003.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1977; UP037.003.003.00006 (Box 3)
    Complete
  - Commencement Programs, 1978; UP037.003.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1979; UP037.003.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1980; UP037.003.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1981; UP037.003.003.00010 (Box 3)
    Missing: School of Nutrition
  - Commencement Programs, 1982; UP037.003.003.00011 (Box 3)
    Missing: School of Nutrition, School of Medicine
  - Commencement Programs, 1983; UP037.003.003.00012 (Box 3)
    Missing: Fletcher School, School of Nutrition, School of Medicine, School of Veterinary Medicine
  - Commencement Programs, 1984; UP037.003.003.00013 (Box 3)
    Missing: Fletcher School, School of Nutrition, School of Dental Medicine, School of Veterinary Medicine
  - Commencement Programs, 1985; UP037.003.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1986; UP037.003.003.00015 (Box 3)
    Missing: School of Nutrition, School of Dental Medicine, Fletcher School
  - Commencement Programs, 1987; UP037.003.003.00016 (Box 3)
    Missing: School of Dental Medicine, Fletcher School
  - Commencement Programs, 1988; UP037.003.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1989; UP037.003.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1990; UP037.003.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Commencement Programs, 1973; UP037.003.003.00020 (Box 3)
    Dental School
  - Commencement Programs, 1991; UP037.003.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1992; UP037.003.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1993; UP037.003.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1994; UP037.003.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1995; UP037.003.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1996; UP037.003.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1997; UP037.003.004.00007 (Box 4)
    Includes International Dental School
  - Commencement Programs, 1998; UP037.003.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1999; UP037.003.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 2000; UP037.003.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - School of Medicine, The Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 2001-05-20; UP037.003.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 2001-05-20; UP037.003.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 2001-05-20; UP037.003.005.00003 (Box 5)
    68th Commencement Exercises.
  - School of Veterinary Medicine, 2001-05-20; UP037.003.005.00004 (Box 5)
    19th Commencement Exercises.
  - School of Nutrition Science and Policy, 2001-05-20; UP037.003.005.00005 (Box 5)
    20th Commencement Exercises.
  - School of Nutrition Science and Policy, 2002; UP037.003.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 2002; UP037.003.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine, 2002; UP037.003.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 2002; UP037.003.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 2002; UP037.003.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Commencement Programs, 2003; UP037.003.005.00028 (Box 5)
    Complete: Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, School of Medicine, and Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, and School of Dental Medicine
  - The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 2004; UP037.003.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine, 2004; UP037.003.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - The Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 2004; UP037.003.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - School of Nutrition, 2004; UP037.003.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 2004; UP037.003.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 2005; UP037.003.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - School of Nutrition, 2005; UP037.003.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine, 2005; UP037.003.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 2005; UP037.003.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - The Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 2005; UP037.003.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 2006; UP037.003.005.00021 (Box 5)
    138th Commencement.
  - School of Veterinary Medicine, 2006; UP037.003.005.00022 (Box 5)
    24th Commencement.
  - The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 2006; UP037.003.005.00023 (Box 5)
    73rd Commencement.
  - School of Nutrition, 2006; UP037.003.005.00024 (Box 5)
    25th Commencement.
  - The Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 2006; UP037.003.005.00025 (Box 5)
    114th Commencement, School of Medicine; 26th Commencement, Sackler School.
  - Commencement Programs, 2007; UP037.003.005.00026 (Box 5)
    Complete: Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, School of Dental Medicine, School of Medicine, and Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences.
  - Commencement Programs, 2008; UP037.003.005.00027 (Box 5)
    Complete: Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, School of Medicine, and Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, and School of Dental Medicine,